

Oscar Guido Delgado

#### CONTACT

Phone: +52 443 448 0968

Email: oscar.guido.delgado@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://oscarguido.github.io/portfolio/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/oscarguido/

### SKILLS

Problem solving
Teamwork
Punctuality
Patience
PHP
Linux
Flutter
Version Control Git

# LANGUAGES

- Spanish: Mother tongue.
- English: Speak, listen, and write (60%).

#### **PROFILE**

Mexican Computer Engineering Intern, with experience in web development, both in backend using PHP and frontend using HTML, CSS, JS and Bootstrap. Also with experience as a mobile application developer with Flutter and with Android Studio using Java as a language.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Faculty of Electrical Engineering, UMSNH.** 2015-2020. B. Eng. in Computer Engineering.

# **EXPERIENCE**

Mobile application developer. Everhard Real Estate.

August, 2020 - January, 2021. Internship.

Responsible for:

- Design and creation of databases in MySQL.
- Backend PHP and MySQL.
- Development of Android mobile applications in Java.
- Development of multiplatform mobile applications in Flutter

Boss: E.E. José Alfredo Bravo Castañeda.

#### Web Developer. Freelance.

August, 2020 - date.

As a freelancer I have worked on small projects such as:

- Static web page development with HTML, CSS and JS.
- Frontend development with HTML, CSS, JS and Bootstrap.
- Creating analytical applications with QlikSense and SQL Server

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Flutter: Your complete development guide for IOS and Android. Udemy. October, 2020.

#### Python Programming.

Faculty of Electrical Engineering. June, 2019.

# **Android Application Development.**

Armaxing. November, 2017.